[
    {
        "question": "Who is the brand ambassador of Nivia India?",
        "optionA": "Anushka Sharma",
        "optionB": "Alia Bhatt",
        "optionC": "Taapsee Pannu",
        "optionD": "Shraddha Kapoor",
        "answer": "Taapsee Pannu"
    },

    {
        "question": "Pumpkin is the national vegetable of which these countries?",
        "optionA": "USA",
        "optionB": "England",
        "optionC": "India",
        "optionD": "Russia",
        "answer": "India"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which Comic character is the alternate of The Flash(DC) in the Marvel Universe?",
        "optionA": "Iron man",
        "optionB": "Quicksilver",
        "optionC": "Magneto",
        "optionD": "Hawkeye",
        "answer": "Quicksilver"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which is the second largest cryptocurrency by market capitalisation after bitcoin?",
        "optionA": "Litecoin",
        "optionB": "Bitcoin Cash",
        "optionC": "Ethereum",
        "optionD": "Ripple",
        "answer": "Ethereum"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these is the first computer animated(3D) feature film?",
        "optionA": "A bugs life",
        "optionB": "Toy Story",
        "optionC": "Shrek",
        "optionD": "Finding Nemo",
        "answer": "Toy Story"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the value of 'g'(acceleration due to gravity) at the centre of earth?",
        "optionA": "9.8",
        "optionB": "10",
        "optionC": "0",
        "optionD": "4.9",
        "answer": "0"
    },

    {
        "question": "Where is the smallest bone in the human body?",
        "optionA": "The Chest",
        "optionB": "The Ear",
        "optionC": "The Legs",
        "optionD": "The Hands",
        "answer": "The Ear"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which country won the 2006 fifa world cup?",
        "optionA": "France",
        "optionB": "Italy",
        "optionC": "Spain",
        "optionD": "Germany",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },

    {
        "question": "'Once you pop you can't stop' is the tagline of which of these companies?",
        "optionA": "Poppins",
        "optionB": "Tic Tac",
        "optionC": "Doritos",
        "optionD": "Pringles",
        "answer": "Pringles"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who launched the bolo app in india to help children in rural india with thier reading skills?",
        "optionA": "Facebook",
        "optionB": "Infosys",
        "optionC": "Microsoft",
        "optionD": "Google",
        "answer": "Google"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which country has scored highest-ever t20 international score?",
        "optionA": "Afghanistan",
        "optionB": "West Indies",
        "optionC": "Australia",
        "optionD": "India",
        "answer": "Afghanistan"
    },

    {
        "question": "Whatâ€™s the capital of Australia?",
        "optionA": "Sydney",
        "optionB": "Melbourne",
        "optionC": "Canberra",
        "optionD": "Brisbane",
        "answer": "Canberra"
    },

    {
        "question": "How many squares are there on a chess board?",
        "optionA": "128",
        "optionB": "64",
        "optionC": "32",
        "optionD": "256",
        "answer": "64"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who invented the electric light bulb?",
        "optionA": "Tom Cruise",
        "optionB": "Barack Obama",
        "optionC": "Wole Soyinka",
        "optionD": "Thomas Edison",
        "answer": "Thomas Edison"
    },

    {
        "question": "What are the first three words of the bible?",
        "optionA": "be with everyone",
        "optionB": "Again Jesus asked",
        "optionC": "In the beginning",
        "optionD": "At that time",
        "answer": "In the beginning"
    }
]